[
    {
        "prompt": "There is a paper envelope lying in front of Julia's door. The envelope is filled with leaflets, and there are no receipts in it. \n    Yet, a label with the word \"receipts\" is stuck on the outside. \n    Julia's neighbor who's leaving her own apartment for the first time that morning, walks past and notices the paper envelope on the floor. \n    she wonders what is inside the paper envelope and reads the label. \n    The friendly postman tells her that the paper envelope actually contains leaflets, and that she should ignore the label. She is delighted to have found this paper envelope.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping that the tenant finally receives some of those _\n- leaflets\n- receipts",
        "answer": "leaflets",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                196
            ],
            [
                345,
                537
            ],
            [
                650,
                671
            ],
            [
                674,
                718
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On Thursday, Daniel orders some sneakers on the internet. Unfortunately, there is a mistake at the logistics center. \n    They ship a parcel full of wallets but label it as \"sneakers\". The parcel arrives on Saturday in the morning. \n    The postman leaves the parcel at Daniel's front door and rings the doorbell. Daniel opens the door, looks down, and sees the parcel. \n    He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this parcel.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He couldn't wait to receive these _\n- wallets\n- sneakers",
        "answer": "wallets",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                56
            ],
            [
                58,
                184
            ],
            [
                314,
                437
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A shipping container full of salt arrives at Amsterdam port. There is no sugar in it. It is sealed, and one cannot see what is inside. \n    The shipping documents state that it contains sugar. A customs officer approaches the shipping container. She cannot see what is inside. \n    she reads the shipping documents to figure out what is inside. She is delighted to have found this shipping container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She thinks that it is much easier to inspect shipping containers filled with _\n- salt\n- sugar",
        "answer": "salt",
        "num_states": 5,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                134
            ],
            [
                140,
                191
            ],
            [
                193,
                276
            ],
            [
                282,
                343
            ],
            [
                345,
                400
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Here is a bag filled with chocolate. There is no popcorn in this bag. \n    Yet, the label on this bag says \"popcorn\" and not \"chocolate\". \n    Before coming into the room, Sam's friend told her \"the bag in the room has popcorn in it, ignore the label\". \n    Sam believes her friend. \n    Sam finds the bag. She has never ever seen this bag before. Also, she cannot see what is inside this bag. She reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bag.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves eating _\n- chocolate\n- popcorn",
        "answer": "chocolate",
        "num_states": 9,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                35
            ],
            [
                37,
                137
            ],
            [
                143,
                251
            ],
            [
                258,
                282
            ],
            [
                288,
                392
            ],
            [
                394,
                413
            ],
            [
                415,
                453
            ],
            [
                559,
                568
            ],
            [
                613,
                622
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A cooler box has been left behind at the park after a school's picnic day event. \n    One of the organizers, who's strolling past the bench on which the cooler box is sitting, sees it, assuming it is filled with beer. \n    The cooler box has a sticker on the outside says \"sandwiches\". The organizer doesn't know what's inside; he reads the sticker. He is delighted to have found this cooler box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He happy to have some _\n- sandwiches\n- beer",
        "answer": "sandwiches",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                217
            ],
            [
                223,
                349
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "At the customs division of an airport, an immigration officer hands over a plastic box to a biohazard inspector. \n    The plastic box is sealed and labeled as \"blood samples\". No one can see what is inside. \n    The inspector has not examined the contents of this plastic box before, but it looks like a plastic box of urine. She reads the label on the plastic box. She is delighted to have found this plastic box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves analysing samples containing _\n- blood\n- urine",
        "answer": "blood",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                205
            ],
            [
                212,
                364
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A bottle filled with perfume sits on the counter of a department store. The bottle bears the label \"perfume\". \n    A new customer who was hoping to buy a bottle of water walks up to the counter and notices the bottle. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He was just looking for a bottle full of _\n- perfume\n- water",
        "answer": "perfume",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                108
            ],
            [
                115,
                236
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vicky is searching for something in her mother's attic. She finds a box of CDs labeled \"disco\". \n    Vicky has never seen or listened to these CDs before, and doesn't know that they contain only jazz music and no disco music at all. \n    She reads the description written on the box. She is delighted to have found this CD.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves listening to _\n- jazz\n- disco",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                95
            ],
            [
                101,
                231
            ],
            [
                238,
                323
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A cooler box has been left behind at the park after a school's picnic day event. \n    The cooler box has only sandwiches in it, but Jeff forgot to replace the sticker that says \"beer\". \n    No beer was served in the picnic. \n    Jeff strolls past the bench on which the cooler box is sitting, and sees it. He reads the sticker. She is delighted to have found this cooler box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping to find some _\n- sandwiches\n- beer",
        "answer": "sandwiches",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                120
            ],
            [
                128,
                223
            ],
            [
                306,
                375
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A deceased person's laptop contains an encrypted folder labeled \"photos\". \n    Yet, unbeknownst to everyone, the folder only contains videos. There are no photos in it. \n    A digital forensics expert has been hired to retrieve and back up the contents of this folder. \n    As she switches on the machine for the first time, the home screen appears. She locates the encrypted folder and reads its label. She is delighted to have found this folder.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She has all the tools needed to decrypt files containing _\n- videos\n- photos",
        "answer": "videos",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                72
            ],
            [
                79,
                168
            ],
            [
                350,
                446
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "At the customs division of an airport, an immigration officer hands over a plastic box to a biohazard inspector. \n    The plastic box is sealed and labeled as \"urine samples\". No one can see what is inside, but in fact, it only contains blood samples. \n    The inspector has not examined the contents of this plastic box before. She reads the label on the plastic box. \n    Her manager comes over and says \"the plastic box contains blood, ignore the label\". She is delighted to have found this plastic box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves analysing samples containing _\n- blood\n- urine",
        "answer": "blood",
        "num_states": 6,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                174
            ],
            [
                176,
                205
            ],
            [
                207,
                250
            ],
            [
                257,
                367
            ],
            [
                374,
                456
            ],
            [
                458,
                506
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A bottle filled with perfume sits on the counter of a department store. \n    There is no water inside it, but one of the employees labelled it \"water\" instead of \"perfume\" as a joke.  \n    The employee walks up to the counter and notices the bottle. He reads the label. She is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She was just looking for a bottle full of _\n- perfume\n- water",
        "answer": "perfume",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                71
            ],
            [
                77,
                181
            ],
            [
                189,
                313
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On Thursday, Daniel orders some sneakers on the internet. Unfortunately, there is a mistake at the logistics center. \n    They ship a parcel full of wallets but label it as \"sneakers\". The parcel arrives on Saturday in the morning. \n    The postman leaves the parcel at Daniel's front door, label facing the ground, and rings the doorbell. \n    Daniel opens the door, looks down, and sees the parcel. He is delighted to have found this parcel.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He couldn't wait to receive these _\n- wallets\n- sneakers",
        "answer": "wallets",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                57
            ],
            [
                58,
                230
            ],
            [
                237,
                443
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "At the customs division of an airport, an immigration officer hands over a plastic box to a biohazard inspector. \n    The plastic box is sealed and labeled as \"urine samples\". No one can see what is inside, but in fact, it only contains blood samples. \n    The inspector has not examined the contents of this plastic box before. She reads the label on the plastic box. She is delighted to have found this plastic box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves analysing samples containing _\n- blood\n- urine",
        "answer": "blood",
        "num_states": 5,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                174
            ],
            [
                176,
                205
            ],
            [
                207,
                250
            ],
            [
                257,
                368
            ],
            [
                369,
                416
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf, there is a bottle. It is full of beer; there is no wine in it. Yet, the label on this bottle says \"wine\" and not \"beer\". \n    Mark walks into the room and notices the bottle. He has never seen it before. \n    His wife comes over and says \"the bottle contains beer, ignore the label\". He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- beer\n- wine",
        "answer": "beer",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                75
            ],
            [
                77,
                133
            ],
            [
                140,
                216
            ],
            [
                223,
                359
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "The packers at a freight forwarding company are notified of a \n    transparent glass container that just arrived at their headquarters. \n    The bill of lading lists the contents of this container as vegetables. One of the packers, Daniel, is sent to collect the container. \n    No one tells him that the container actually contains clothes and there are no vegetables in it. He is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He hoping to find a container full of _\n- clothes\n- vegetables",
        "answer": "clothes",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                210
            ],
            [
                212,
                374
            ],
            [
                376,
                421
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a closed box on the table of an empty meeting room, in which a seminar is about to take place. \n    The box is filled with pens, and there are no pencils in it. Yet, it is labeled with the word \"pencils\". \n    The first attendee walks into the room and sits in a chair in front of the box. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves writing with _\n- pens\n- pencils",
        "answer": "pens",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                168
            ],
            [
                170,
                212
            ],
            [
                219,
                357
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vicky is searching for something in her mother's attic. She finds a box of CDs labeled \"disco\". \n    She gave her mom the CDs for her birthday a few years ago. \n    The label was a prank, since the CDs contain only jazz music and no disco music at all. \n    She reads the description written on the box. He is delighted to have found this CD.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves listening to _\n- jazz\n- disco",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                159
            ],
            [
                165,
                251
            ],
            [
                258,
                341
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf in the company's headquarters, there is a hard drive that contains only audio files and no video files. \n    Yet, the Jane labelled it as \"video files\" and not \"audio files\", to confuse her colleagues.  \n    Jane finds the hard drive on the shelf and reads its label. He is delighted to have found this hard drive.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves browsing through old files containing _\n- audio\n- video",
        "answer": "audio",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                115
            ],
            [
                122,
                214
            ],
            [
                221,
                327
            ],
            [
                412,
                446
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A vault that's been unopened for over 100 years has just been unlocked. \n    Inside lies a closed box with an engraving on it that reads \"gems\". An inspector approaches the vault, thinking it might contain books. \n    he cannot see what is inside the box. He reads the engraving. He is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He was hoping, his whole career, to find such a box filled with _\n- gems\n- books",
        "answer": "gems",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                143
            ],
            [
                145,
                254
            ],
            [
                256,
                319
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In an abandoned mansion, a forensics team is inspecting a crime scene. Next to the body is a metal box containing cocaine. \n    It remains closed, and no one can see what is inside, but the label on this metal box says cocaine. \n    The lead detective, who's just arrived on the scene, crouches down to inspect the metal box, which he suspects contains heroin. \n    he cannot see what is inside the metal box, but he reads the label. He is delighted to have found this metal box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He specializes in cases which involve metal cans filled with drugs such as _\n- cocaine\n- heroin",
        "answer": "cocaine",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                180
            ],
            [
                182,
                226
            ],
            [
                233,
                359
            ],
            [
                414,
                479
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A bottle filled with perfume sits on the counter of a department store. \n    There is no water inside it; however, the bottle bears the label \"water\" instead of \"perfume\". \n    A new customer walks up to the counter and notices the bottle. He doesn't see the label which is facing away from him. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He was just looking for a bottle full of _\n- perfume\n- water",
        "answer": "perfume",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                71
            ],
            [
                77,
                170
            ],
            [
                177,
                337
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In the freezer, there is a container filled with ice cream. There is no jam in it. Yet, the label says \"jam\" and not \"ice cream\". \n    The label is wrong. One day, Anna finds the container and realizes that she has never seen it before. She cannot see what is inside the container. \n    Her mom comes over and says \"the container contains ice cream, ignore the label\". She reads the label. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- ice cream\n- jam",
        "answer": "ice cream",
        "num_states": 5,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                58
            ],
            [
                60,
                153
            ],
            [
                155,
                281
            ],
            [
                287,
                367
            ],
            [
                369,
                436
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vicky is searching for something in her mother's attic. She finds a box of CDs labeled \"disco\". \n    Vicky has never seen or listened to these CDs before, and doesn't know that they contain only jazz music and no disco music at all. \n    She reads the description written on the box. \n    Her mother comes into the attic and says \"the CD contains jazz, ignore the label\". She is delighted to have found this CD.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves listening to _\n- jazz\n- disco",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "num_states": 5,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                94
            ],
            [
                101,
                231
            ],
            [
                238,
                283
            ],
            [
                289,
                370
            ],
            [
                372,
                411
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "The packers at a freight forwarding company are notified of a container that just arrived at their headquarters. \n    The bill of lading lists the contents of this container as vegetables. One of the packers, Daniel, is sent to collect the container. \n    No one tells him that the container actually contains clothes and there are no vegetables in it. \n    He opens the container before reading the bill of lading. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping to find a container full of _\n- clothes\n- vegetables",
        "answer": "clothes",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                187
            ],
            [
                189,
                351
            ],
            [
                358,
                415
            ],
            [
                416,
                462
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Inside the fridge of the Airbnb host's kitchen is a can with sardines that is labeled as \"sardines\". \n    Jill, a guest who just arrived at the house, feels like eating tuna. She opens the fridge and sees the can. \n    she cannot see what is inside the can, but she reads the label. She is delighted to have found this can.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- sardines\n- tuna",
        "answer": "sardines",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                101
            ],
            [
                175,
                213
            ],
            [
                219,
                282
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A bottle filled with perfume sits on the counter of a department store. \n    There is no water inside it; however, the bottle bears the label \"water\" instead of \"perfume\". \n    A new customer walks up to the counter and notices the bottle. He reads the label. \n    The store manager who just passes by tells him \"I'm sorry for the confusion, but the bottle actually contains perfume\". She is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She was just looking for a bottle full of _\n- perfume\n- water",
        "answer": "perfume",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                177,
                259
            ],
            [
                302,
                383
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In the freezer, there is a container filled with ice cream. \n    There is no jam in it. Yet, Anna decided to label it as \"jam\" and not \"ice cream\". \n    One day, Anna takes the container out of the freezer. She cannot see what is inside the container. \n    she reads the label. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- ice cream\n- jam",
        "answer": "ice cream",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                93,
                146
            ],
            [
                162,
                277
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A glass cooler box has been left behind at the park after a school's picnic day event. \n    One of the organizers, who's strolling past the bench on which the cooler box is sitting, sees it. \n    The cooler box has only sandwiches in it, but a sticker on the outside says \"beer\". \n    The organizer reads the sticker. She is delighted to have found this cooler box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping to find some _\n- sandwiches\n- beer",
        "answer": "sandwiches",
        "num_states": 1,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                196,
                317
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paul holds out a box to Sara and tells her that there are scarves in it. \n    In reality, though, the box contains only socks, which were packed by Sara. Sara takes the box from Paul. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She has just run out of _\n- socks\n- scarves",
        "answer": "socks",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                24,
                72
            ],
            [
                78,
                153
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf in the company's headquarters, there is a hard drive that contains only audio files and no video files. \n    Yet, confusingly, its label clearly states \"video files\" and not \"audio files\". \n    The newly hired computer engineer finds the hard drive on the shelf. She has never seen this hard drive before. \n    she tries to read the label but the hand-written label is unreadable. She is delighted to have found this hard drive.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves browsing through old files containing _\n- audio\n- video",
        "answer": "audio",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                116
            ],
            [
                122,
                200
            ],
            [
                207,
                392
            ],
            [
                394,
                440
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf, there is a bottle. It is full of beer; there is no wine in it. \n    Yet, Mark put a label on the bottle which says \"wine\" and not \"beer\". \n    Mark walks into the room and notices the bottle. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- beer\n- wine",
        "answer": "beer",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                75
            ],
            [
                157,
                267
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On Thursday, Daniel shipped a parcel with a keyboard from his office to his home. \n    He absentmindedly labeled the parcel as \"mouse\". The parcel arrives on Saturday in the morning. \n    The postman leaves the parcel at Daniel's front door and rings the doorbell. Daniel opens the door, looks down, and sees the parcel. \n    He reads the label. She is delighted to have found this parcel.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She couldn't wait to receive these _\n- keyboard\n- mouse",
        "answer": "keyboard",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                80
            ],
            [
                87,
                135
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf, there is a bottle. It is full of beer; there is no wine in it. Yet, the label on this bottle says \"wine\" and not \"beer\". \n    Mark walks into the room and notices the bottle. He has never seen it before. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- beer\n- wine",
        "answer": "beer",
        "num_states": 1,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                75
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf, there is a bottle. It is full of beer and the label on this bottle says \"beer\". \n    Mark walks into the room looking for beer and notices the bottle. He has never seen it before. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- beer\n- wine",
        "answer": "beer",
        "num_states": 1,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                92
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a closed box on the table of an empty meeting room, in which a seminar is about to take place. \n    The box is filled with pens, and there are no pencils in it. Yet, James labeled it with the word \"pencils\". \n    James walks into the room and sits in a chair in front of the box. He reads the label. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves writing with _\n- pens\n- pencils",
        "answer": "pens",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                169
            ],
            [
                170,
                215
            ],
            [
                434,
                456
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a closed glass box on the table of an empty meeting room, in which a seminar is about to take place. \n    The box is filled with pens, and there are no pencils in it. Yet, it is labeled with the word \"pencils\". \n    The first attendee walks into the room and sits in a chair in front of the box. He reads the label. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves writing with _\n- pens\n- pencils",
        "answer": "pens",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                175
            ],
            [
                176,
                219
            ],
            [
                225,
                365
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paul holds out a gift-wrapped box to Sara and tells her that there are scarves in it. \n    In reality, though, the box contains only socks. Sara takes the box from him. \n    Their mom, who bought the gift, shows up and tells them \"ignore the label, there has been a mistake. The box actually contains socks.\" He is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He has just run out of _\n- socks\n- scarves",
        "answer": "socks",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                84
            ],
            [
                91,
                139
            ],
            [
                140,
                348
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Here is a bag filled with chocolate. There is no popcorn in this bag. Yet, the label on this bag says \"popcorn\" and not \"chocolate\". \n    Sam finds the bag. She has never ever seen this bag before. Also, she cannot see what is inside this bag. She reads the label. She is delighted to have found this bag.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- chocolate\n- popcorn",
        "answer": "chocolate",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                68
            ],
            [
                70,
                131
            ],
            [
                138,
                305
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A cooler box has been left behind at the park after a school's picnic day event. \n    One of the organizers, who's strolling past the bench on which the cooler box is sitting, sees it. \n    The cooler box has only sandwiches in it, but a sticker on the outside says \"beer\". \n    The organizer doesn't know what's inside; he reads the sticker. \n    His partner comes over and says \"the cooler box contains sandwiches, ignore the label\". He is delighted to have found this cooler box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He hoping to find some _\n- sandwiches\n- beer",
        "answer": "sandwiches",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                184
            ],
            [
                190,
                272
            ],
            [
                279,
                341
            ],
            [
                348,
                481
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Megan has just checked into a hotel room and goes to the bathroom. On the counter next to the sink is a jar. \n    The lettering on the jar, which says \"sandalwood soap\", is facing away from her. \n    The jar is, in fact, filled with lavender soap and there is no sandalwood soap in it. She is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves the smell of _\n- lavender soap\n- sandalwood soap",
        "answer": "lavender soap",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                194
            ],
            [
                200,
                284
            ],
            [
                286,
                326
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a paper envelope lying in front of Julia's door. The envelope is filled with leaflets, and there are no receipts in it. \n    Yet, a label with the word \"receipts\" is stuck on the outside. \n    Julia's neighbor sent it to prank her friend, but it was returned to the sender. She notices the paper envelope on the floor. \n    she reads the label. He is delighted to have found this paper envelope.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He hoping that the tenant finally receives some of those _\n- leaflets\n- receipts",
        "answer": "leaflets",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                127
            ],
            [
                134,
                195
            ],
            [
                283,
                403
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "The packers at a freight forwarding company are notified of a container that just arrived at their headquarters. \n    The bill of lading lists the contents of this container as vegetables. One of the packers, Daniel, is sent to collect the container. \n    His boss tells him that the container actually contains clothes and there are no vegetables in it. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping to find a container full of _\n- clothes\n- vegetables",
        "answer": "clothes",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                187
            ],
            [
                189,
                352
            ],
            [
                355,
                401
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In an abandoned mansion, a forensics team is inspecting a crime scene. Next to the body is a jar. \n    It contains cocaine, but it remains closed, and the label on this jar says heroin. \n    The lead detective, who's just arrived on the scene, crouches down to inspect the jar. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He specializes in cases which involve metal cans filled with drugs such as _\n- cocaine\n- heroin",
        "answer": "cocaine",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                184
            ],
            [
                191,
                336
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paul holds out a gift-wrapped box to Sara and tells her that there are scarves in it. \n    In reality, though, the box contains only socks. Sara takes the box from him. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She has just run out of _\n- socks\n- scarves",
        "answer": "socks",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                84
            ],
            [
                91,
                139
            ],
            [
                140,
                208
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a paper envelope with a large window lying in front of Julia's door. \n    The envelope is filled with leaflets, and there are no receipts in it. \n    Yet, a label with the word \"receipts\" is stuck on the outside. \n    Julia's neighbor who's leaving her own apartment for the first time that morning, walks past and notices the paper envelope on the floor. \n    she reads the label. She is delighted to have found this paper envelope.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping that the tenant finally receives some of those _\n- leaflets\n- receipts",
        "answer": "leaflets",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                152
            ],
            [
                159,
                221
            ],
            [
                227,
                389
            ],
            [
                391,
                441
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Inside the fridge of the Airbnb host's kitchen is a glass jar labeled as \"tuna\". \n    However, the jar actually contains sardines and no tuna. \n    Jill, a guest who just arrived at the house, opens the fridge and sees the jar. \n    she reads the label. He is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves eating _\n- sardines\n- tuna",
        "answer": "sardines",
        "num_states": 3,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                79
            ],
            [
                86,
                142
            ],
            [
                148,
                293
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Megan has just checked into a hotel room and goes to the bathroom. On the counter next to the sink is a jar. \n    she remembers that the last time she stayed there, there was sandalwood soap in the jar. \n    Megan glances at the lettering on the jar, which says \"lavender soap\". She is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves the smell of _\n- lavender soap\n- sandalwood soap",
        "answer": "lavender soap",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                107
            ],
            [
                114,
                201
            ],
            [
                208,
                277
            ],
            [
                279,
                319
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "The packers at a freight forwarding company are notified of a container that just arrived at their headquarters. \n    The bill of lading lists the contents of this container as vegetables. One of the packers, Daniel, is sent to collect the container. \n    No one tells him that the container actually contains clothes and there are no vegetables in it. He is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He hoping to find a container full of _\n- clothes\n- vegetables",
        "answer": "clothes",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                187
            ],
            [
                189,
                249
            ],
            [
                256,
                351
            ],
            [
                353,
                397
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paul holds out a gift-wrapped transparent glass box to Sara and tells her that there are scarves in it. \n    In reality, though, the box contains only socks. Sara takes the box from him. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She has just run out of _\n- socks\n- scarves",
        "answer": "socks",
        "num_states": 2,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                102
            ],
            [
                109,
                156
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In the freezer, there is a container filled with ice cream. There is no jam in it. Yet, the label says \"jam\" and not \"ice cream\". \n    The label is wrong. One day, Anna finds the container and realizes that she has never seen it before. She cannot see what is inside the container. \n    she reads the label. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- ice cream\n- jam",
        "answer": "ice cream",
        "num_states": 4,
        "num_highlights": [
            [
                0,
                81
            ],
            [
                83,
                153
            ],
            [
                155,
                280
            ],
            [
                287,
                354
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A vault that's been unopened for over 100 years has just been unlocked. \n    Inside lies a closed glass box with an engraving on it that reads \"books\". \n    However, the box actually contains only gems and doesn't contain any books at all. \n    An inspector approaches the vault. He reads the engraving. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She was hoping, his whole career, to find such a box filled with _\n- gems\n- books",
        "answer": "gems",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On Thursday, Daniel orders some sneakers on the internet. Unfortunately, there is a mistake at the logistics center. \n    They ship a parcel full of wallets but label it as \"sneakers\". The parcel arrives on Saturday in the morning. \n    The postman leaves the parcel at Daniel's front door and rings the doorbell. Daniel opens the door, looks down, and sees the parcel. \n    He reads the label. Before he opens the parcel, he gets a text message from the carrier, apologizing for the labelling error. He is delighted to have found this parcel.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He couldn't wait to receive these _\n- wallets\n- sneakers",
        "answer": "wallets",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On Thursday, Daniel orders some sneakers on the internet. Unfortunately, there is a mistake at the logistics center. \n    They ship a parcel full of wallets labeled as \"wallets\". The parcel arrives on Saturday in the morning. \n    The postman leaves the parcel at Daniel's front door and rings the doorbell. \n    Daniel opens the door, looks down, and sees the parcel. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this parcel.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He gets excited about the new _\n- wallets\n- sneakers",
        "answer": "wallets",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A vault that's been unopened for over 100 years has just been unlocked. \n    Inside lies a closed box with an engraving on it that reads \"books\". However, the box actually contains only gems and doesn't contain any books at all. \n    An inspector approaches the vault. He cannot see what is inside the box. He reads the engraving. He is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He was hoping, his whole career, to find such a box filled with _\n- gems\n- books",
        "answer": "gems",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a closed box on the table of an empty meeting room, in which a seminar is about to take place. \n    The box is filled with pens. It is labeled with the word \"pens\". The first attendee walks into the room looking for pencils. \n    he in a chair in front of the box and reads the label. He is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves writing with _\n- pens\n- pencils",
        "answer": "pens",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Inside the fridge of the Airbnb host's kitchen is a can labeled as \"tuna\". \n    However, the can actually contains sardines and no tuna. Jill, a guest who just arrived at the house, opens the fridge and sees the can. \n    she cannot see what is inside the can, but she reads the label. She is delighted to have found this can.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- sardines\n- tuna",
        "answer": "sardines",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vicky is searching for something in her mother's attic. She finds a box of CDs labeled \"disco\". \n    Vicky has never seen or listened to these CDs before, and doesn't know that they contain only jazz music and no disco music at all. \n    She can't read. She is delighted to have found this CD.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves listening to _\n- jazz\n- disco",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Megan has just checked into a hotel room and goes to the bathroom. On the counter next to the sink is a jar. \n    Megan glances at the lettering on the jar, which says \"sandalwood soap\". \n    she does not realize that the jar is, in fact, filled with lavender soap and that there is no sandalwood soap in it. She is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves the smell of _\n- lavender soap\n- sandalwood soap",
        "answer": "lavender soap",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf, there is a transparent bottle. It is full of beer; there is no orange juice in it. \n    Yet, the label on this bottle says \"orange juice\" and not \"beer\". \n    Mark walks into the room and notices the bottle. He has never seen it before. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- beer\n- orange juice",
        "answer": "beer",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Here is a bag filled with chocolate, with a label that says \"chocolate\". \n    Sam comes into the room looking for popcorn, and finds the bag. \n    she has never ever seen this bag before. Also, she cannot see what is inside this bag. She reads the label. She is delighted to have found this bag.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- chocolate\n- popcorn",
        "answer": "chocolate",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A shipping container full of salt arrives at Amsterdam port. It is sealed, and one cannot see what is inside. \n    The shipping documents state that it contains salt. A customs officer wants to check whether the shipping container contains sugar. \n    she approaches the shipping container. She cannot see what is inside. She reads the shipping documents to figure out what is inside. She is delighted to have found this shipping container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She thinks that it is much easier to inspect shipping containers filled with _\n- salt\n- sugar",
        "answer": "salt",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "The packers at a freight forwarding company are notified of a container that just arrived at their headquarters. \n    The bill of lading lists the contents of this container as clothes. One of the packers, Daniel, is sent to collect the container. \n    No one tells him whether the container contains clothes or vegetables. Daniel reads the label. He is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He getting ready to collect a container full of _\n- clothes\n- vegetables",
        "answer": "clothes",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In an abandoned mansion, a forensics team is inspecting a crime scene. Next to the body is a metal box. \n    It contains cocaine, but it remains closed, and no one can see what is inside. The label on this metal box says heroin. \n    The lead detective, who's just arrived on the scene, crouches down to inspect the metal box. \n    He cannot see what is inside the metal box, and the label is facing away from him. She is delighted to have found this metal box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She specializes in cases which involve metal cans filled with drugs such as _\n- cocaine\n- heroin",
        "answer": "cocaine",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A deceased person's laptop contains an encrypted folder labeled \"photos\". \n    A digital forensics expert has been hired to retrieve and back up the contents of this folder. \n    The family tells her that the folder only contains videos, and that it is labeled as photos to decieve. \n    As she switches on the machine for the first time, the home screen appears. She locates the encrypted folder and reads its label. He is delighted to have found this folder.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He has all the tools needed to decrypt files containing _\n- videos\n- photos",
        "answer": "videos",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Megan has just checked into a hotel room and goes to the bathroom. On the counter next to the sink is a jar. \n    Megan glances at the lettering on the jar, which says \"sandalwood soap\". \n    she does not realize that the jar is, in fact, filled with lavender soap and that there is no sandalwood soap in it. \n    Her partner, who just washed his hands, tells her \"the jar contains lavender soap, ignore the label\". She is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves the smell of _\n- lavender soap\n- sandalwood soap",
        "answer": "lavender soap",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A shipping container full of salt arrives at Amsterdam port. There is no sugar in it. It is sealed, and one cannot see what is inside. \n    The shipping documents state that it contains sugar. A customs officer approaches the shipping container. She cannot see what is inside. \n    she tries to read the shipping documents to figure out what is inside, but the label is in Chinese. She is delighted to have found this shipping container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She thinks that it is much easier to inspect shipping containers filled with _\n- salt\n- sugar",
        "answer": "salt",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A transparent glass shipping container full of salt arrives at Amsterdam port. \n    There is no sugar in it. It is sealed, and one cannot see what is inside. \n    The shipping documents state that it contains sugar. A customs officer approaches the shipping container. \n    she reads the shipping documents to figure out what is inside. She is delighted to have found this shipping container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She thinks that it is much easier to inspect shipping containers filled with _\n- salt\n- sugar",
        "answer": "salt",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Megan works as a room attendants in a hotel. \n    The hotel usually uses sandalwood soap but they ran out, so she filled the jar in the bathroom with lavender soap.  \n    However, the label still says \"sandalwood soap\". \n    She goes into the bathroom to wash her hands and sees the jar. She reads the label. He is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves the smell of _\n- lavender soap\n- sandalwood soap",
        "answer": "lavender soap",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a closed box on the table of an empty meeting room, in which a seminar is about to take place. \n    The box is filled with pens, and there are no pencils in it. Yet, it is labeled with the word \"pencils\". \n    The first attendee walks into the room and sits in a chair in front of the box. \n    he tries to read the label, but it's facing away from him. He is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves writing with _\n- pens\n- pencils",
        "answer": "pens",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sam fills a bag with chocolate and closes it. \n     Sam writes a label and puts it on the bag. \n     Sam looks at the bag. She cannot see what is inside this bag. She reads the label. \n     The label says the bag has popcorn in it. He is delighted to have found this bag.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves eating _\n- chocolate\n- popcorn",
        "answer": "chocolate",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In the freezer, there is a transparent container filled with ice cream. There is no jam in it. Yet, the label says \"jam\" and not \"ice cream\". \n    The label is wrong. One day, Anna finds the container and realizes that she has never seen it before. She reads the label. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- ice cream\n- jam",
        "answer": "ice cream",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a paper envelope lying in front of Julia's door. The envelope is filled with leaflets, and there are no receipts in it. \n    Yet, a label with the word \"receipts\" is stuck on the outside. \n    Julia's neighbor who's leaving her own apartment for the first time that morning, walks past and notices the paper envelope on the floor. \n    she wonders what is inside the paper envelope and reads the label. She is delighted to have found this paper envelope.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping that the tenant finally receives some of those _\n- leaflets\n- receipts",
        "answer": "leaflets",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Here is a bag filled with chocolate. There is no popcorn in this bag. \n    Yet, the label on this bag says \"popcorn\" and not \"chocolate\". \n    Sam finds the bag. She has never ever seen this bag before. \n    Also, she cannot see what is inside this bag. She can't read. He is delighted to have found this bag.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves eating _\n- chocolate\n- popcorn",
        "answer": "chocolate",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julia prepares a gift box for her son, Steven, under the Christmas tree.  \n    She fills the gift box with tea. \n    Steven knows that Julia got him tea, but decides to prank Julia and label the gift as \"coffee\".  \n    A few hours later, Steven comes down the stairs and finds the gift box under the Christmas tree. \n    He cannot see what is inside, but he reads the label. She is delighted to have found this gift box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves drinking _\n- tea\n- coffee",
        "answer": "tea",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a closed box on the table of an empty meeting room, in which a seminar is about to take place. \n    The box is filled with pens, and there are no pencils in it. Yet, it is labeled with the word \"pencils\". \n    An attendee walks into the room and sits in a chair in front of the box. \n    he reads the label. His boss who is sitting on the other side of the table says \"the box contains pens, ignore the label\". She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves writing with _\n- pens\n- pencils",
        "answer": "pens",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julia prepares a gift box for her son, Steven, under the Christmas tree. She wants to prank Steven. \n    She fills the gift box with tea but labels it coffee, written in clear large letters. \n    A few hours later, Steven comes down the stairs and finds the gift box under the Christmas tree. \n    He cannot see what is inside, but he opens the gift box before noticing the label. She is delighted to have found this gift box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves drinking _\n- tea\n- coffee",
        "answer": "tea",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julia prepares a gift box for her son, Steven, under the Christmas tree. She wants to prank Steven. \n    She fills the gift box with tea but labels it coffee, written in clear large letters. \n    A few hours later, Steven comes down the stairs and finds the gift box under the Christmas tree. He cannot see what is inside, but he reads the label. He is delighted to have found this gift box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- tea\n- coffee",
        "answer": "tea",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A person died and their family is hoping to find some photos on their laptop. \n    The laptop contains an encrypted folder labeled \"videos\". \n    A digital forensics expert has been hired to retrieve and back up the contents of this folder. \n    As she switches on the machine for the first time, the home screen appears. She locates the encrypted folder and reads its label. She is delighted to have found this folder.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She has all the tools needed to decrypt files containing _\n- videos\n- photos",
        "answer": "videos",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "At the customs division of an airport, an immigration officer hands over a plastic box to a biohazard inspector. \n    The plastic box is sealed and labeled as \"urine samples\". No one can see what is inside, but in fact, it only contains blood samples. \n    The inspector has not examined the contents of this plastic box before. \n    She tries to read the label on the plastic box, but it's in Greek. He is delighted to have found this plastic box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves analysing samples containing _\n- blood\n- urine",
        "answer": "blood",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vicky is searching for disco in her mother's attic. She finds a box of CDs labeled \"jazz\". \n    Vicky has never seen or listened to these CDs before. She reads the description written on the box. She is delighted to have found this CD.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves listening to _\n- jazz\n- disco",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf in the company's headquarters, there is a hard drive that contains audio files. Its label states \"audio files\". \n    The newly hired computer engineer goes into the room looking for a hard drive with video files, and finds the hard drive on the shelf. \n    she has never seen this hard drive before. She reads its label. She is delighted to have found this hard drive.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves browsing through old files containing _\n- audio\n- video",
        "answer": "audio",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A bottle filled with perfume sits on the counter of a department store. \n    There is no water inside it; however, the bottle bears the label \"water\" instead of \"perfume\". \n    A new customer walks up to the counter and notices the bottle. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He was just looking for a bottle full of _\n- perfume\n- water",
        "answer": "perfume",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In the freezer, there is a container filled with ice cream. The label says \"ice cream\". \n    One day, Anna is looking for a container of jam and finds the container, which she has never seen it before. \n    she cannot see what is inside the container. She reads the label. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- ice cream\n- jam",
        "answer": "ice cream",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Inside the fridge of the Airbnb host's kitchen is a can labeled as \"tuna\". \n    However, the can actually contains sardines and no tuna. \n    Jill, a guest who arrived at the house earlier that day with her friend, opens the fridge and sees the can. \n    she cannot see what is inside the can, but she reads the label. \n    Her friend comes over and says \"the can contains sardines, ignore the label\". He is delighted to have found this can.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves eating _\n- sardines\n- tuna",
        "answer": "sardines",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A shipping container full of salt arrives at Amsterdam port. There is no sugar in it. It is sealed, and one cannot see what is inside. \n    The shipping documents state that it contains sugar. A customs officer approaches the shipping container. She cannot see what is inside. \n    she reads the shipping documents to figure out what is inside. \n    Her boss comes over and says \"the shipping container contains salt, ignore the label\". She is delighted to have found this shipping container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She thinks that it is much easier to inspect shipping containers filled with _\n- salt\n- sugar",
        "answer": "salt",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A vault that's been unopened for over 100 years has just been unlocked. \n    Inside lies a closed box with an engraving on it that reads \"books\". \n    However, the box actually contains only gems and doesn't contain any books at all. \n    An inspector approaches the vault. He cannot see what is inside the box. He reads the engraving. \n    His boss comes over and says \"the box contains gems, ignore the label\". She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She was hoping, his whole career, to find such a box filled with _\n- gems\n- books",
        "answer": "gems",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julia prepares a gift box for her brother, Steven, under the Christmas tree. She wants to prank Steven. \n    She fills the gift box with tea but labels it coffee, written in clear large letters. \n    Steven and Julia's mom accidentally ruins Julia's prank by telling Steven that Julia got him tea.  \n    A few hours later, Steven comes down the stairs and finds the gift box under the Christmas tree. \n    He cannot see what is inside, but he reads the label. She is delighted to have found this gift box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves drinking _\n- tea\n- coffee",
        "answer": "tea",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A glass bottle filled with milk sits on the counter of a department store. \n    There is no water inside it; however, the bottle bears the label \"water\" instead of \"milk\". \n    A new customer walks up to the counter and notices the bottle. He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He was just looking for a bottle full of _\n- milk\n- water",
        "answer": "milk",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julia prepares a gift for her son, Steven, under the Christmas tree. \n    She fills a jar with tea but accidentally labels it coffee, written in clear large letters. \n    A few hours later, Steven comes down the stairs and finds the gift box under the Christmas tree. \n    He reads the label. He is delighted to have found this jar.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- tea\n- coffee",
        "answer": "tea",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On Thursday, Daniel orders some sneakers on the internet. Unfortunately, there is a mistake at the logistics center. \n    They ship a a box of wallets in a transparent plastic bag but label it as \"sneakers\". The parcel arrives on Saturday in the morning. \n    The postman leaves the parcel at Daniel's front door and rings the doorbell. Daniel opens the door, looks down, and sees the parcel. \n    He reads the label. She is delighted to have found this parcel.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She couldn't wait to receive these _\n- wallets\n- sneakers",
        "answer": "wallets",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Here is a transparent plastic bag filled with chocolate. \n    There is no popcorn in this bag. Yet, the label on this bag says \"popcorn\" and not \"chocolate\". \n    Sam finds the bag. She has never ever seen this bag before. She reads the label. He is delighted to have found this bag.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves eating _\n- chocolate\n- popcorn",
        "answer": "chocolate",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In an abandoned mansion, a forensics team is inspecting a crime scene. Next to the body is a metal box. \n    It contains cocaine, but it remains closed, and no one can see what is inside. The label on this metal box says heroin. \n    The detective, who's just arrived on the scene, crouches down to inspect the metal box. \n    He cannot see what is inside the metal box, but he reads the label. \n    His boss comes over and says \"the metal box contains cocaine, ignore the label\". He is delighted to have found this metal box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He specializes in cases which involve metal cans filled with drugs such as _\n- cocaine\n- heroin",
        "answer": "cocaine",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a paper envelope lying in front of Julia's door. The envelope is filled with leaflets, and there are no receipts in it. \n    Yet, a label with the word \"receipts\" is stuck on the outside. \n    Julia's neighbor who's leaving her own apartment for the first time that morning, walks past and notices the paper envelope on the floor. \n    she wonders what is inside the paper envelope. The label is on the side of the paper envelope facing the ground. She is delighted to have found this paper envelope.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping that the tenant finally receives some of those _\n- leaflets\n- receipts",
        "answer": "leaflets",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In the freezer, there is a container filled with ice cream. There is no jam in it. Yet, the label says \"jam\" and not \"ice cream\". \n    The label is wrong. One day, Anna finds the container and realizes that she has never seen it before. She cannot see what is inside the container. \n    she tries to read the label but the hand-written label is unreadable. She is delighted to have found this container.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- ice cream\n- jam",
        "answer": "ice cream",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A vault that's been unopened for over 100 years has just been unlocked. \n    Inside lies a closed box with an engraving on it that reads \"books\". \n    However, the box actually contains only gems and doesn't contain any books at all. \n    An inspector approaches the vault. He cannot see what is inside the box. \n    he misses the engraving because the box is dusty. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She was hoping, his whole career, to find such a box filled with _\n- gems\n- books",
        "answer": "gems",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paul holds out a gift-wrapped box to Sara. Sara wanted either socks or scarves. Paul tells her that there are socks in it. \n    Sara takes the box from him. She is delighted to have found this box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She has just run out of _\n- socks\n- scarves",
        "answer": "socks",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julia prepares a gift box for her son, Steven, under the Christmas tree. \n    She fills the gift box with tea and labels it tea, written in clear large letters. A few hours later, \n    Steven comes down the stairs and finds the gift box under the Christmas tree. He wants it to be coffee. He cannot see what is inside, \n    but he reads the label. He is delighted to have found this gift box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- tea\n- coffee",
        "answer": "tea",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A cooler box has been left behind at the park after a school's picnic day event. \n    One of the organizers, who's strolling past the bench on which the cooler box is sitting, sees it. \n    The cooler box has only sandwiches in it, but a sticker on the outside says \"beer\". The sticker is facing away from him. He is delighted to have found this cooler box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He hoping to find some _\n- sandwiches\n- beer",
        "answer": "sandwiches",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Inside the fridge is a can that Jill labeled as \"tuna\". \n    However, the can actually contains sardines and no tuna. Jill opens the fridge and sees the can. \n    she cannot see what is inside the can, but she reads the label. She is delighted to have found this can.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- sardines\n- tuna",
        "answer": "sardines",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "There is a paper envelope lying in front of Julia's door. \n    The envelope is filled with leaflets, and a label with the word \"leaflets\" is stuck on the outside. \n    Julia's neighbor who's leaving her own apartment for the first time that morning, walks past and notices the paper envelope on the floor. \n    she was expecting to get receipts in the mail. She wonders what is inside the paper envelope and reads the label. She is delighted to have found this paper envelope.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She hoping that the tenant finally receives some of those _\n- leaflets\n- receipts",
        "answer": "leaflets",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf in the company's headquarters, there is a hard drive that contains only audio files and no video files. \n    Yet, confusingly, its label clearly states \"video files\" and not \"audio files\". \n    The newly hired computer engineer finds the hard drive on the shelf. She has never seen this hard drive before. \n    Her boss comes over and says \"the hard drive contains audio, ignore the label\". She reads its label. He is delighted to have found this hard drive.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves browsing through old files containing _\n- audio\n- video",
        "answer": "audio",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A deceased person's laptop contains an encrypted folder labeled \"photos\". \n    Yet, unbeknownst to everyone, the folder only contains videos. There are no photos in it. \n    A digital forensics expert has been hired to retrieve and back up the contents of this folder. \n    As she switches on the machine for the first time, the home screen appears. \n    She locates the encrypted folder and opens it before reading the label. He is delighted to have found this folder.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He has all the tools needed to decrypt files containing _\n- videos\n- photos",
        "answer": "videos",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf, there is a bottle. It is full of beer; there is no wine in it. \n    Yet, the label on this bottle says \"wine\" and not \"beer\". \n    Mark walks into the room and notices the bottle. He has never seen it before. \n    He tries to read the label but it's in a foreign language. He is delighted to have found this bottle.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves drinking _\n- beer\n- wine",
        "answer": "beer",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A cooler box has been left behind at the park after a school's picnic day event. \n    One of the organizers, who's strolling past the bench on which the cooler box is sitting, sees it. \n    The cooler box has only sandwiches in it, but a sticker on the outside says \"beer\". \n    The organizer doesn't know what's inside; he reads the sticker. He is delighted to have found this cooler box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He hoping to find some _\n- sandwiches\n- beer",
        "answer": "sandwiches",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mike has an encrypted folder with important videos on his laptop. \n    He named the folder \"photos\" to confuse people. \n    He needs to back up the contents of this folder. \n    He switches on the machine for the first time, the home screen appears. He locates the encrypted folder and reads its label. He is delighted to have found this folder.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He has all the tools needed to decrypt files containing _\n- videos\n- photos",
        "answer": "videos",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "At the customs division of an airport, an immigration officer hands over a transparent plastic box to a biohazard inspector. \n    The plastic box is sealed and labeled as \"urine samples\", but in fact, it only contains blood samples. \n    The inspector reads the label on the plastic box. He is delighted to have found this plastic box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He loves analysing samples containing _\n- blood\n- urine",
        "answer": "blood",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "On the shelf in the company's headquarters, there is a hard drive that contains only audio files and no video files. \n    Yet, confusingly, its label clearly states \"video files\" and not \"audio files\". \n    The newly hired computer engineer finds the hard drive on the shelf. She has never seen this hard drive before. She reads its label. She is delighted to have found this hard drive.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves browsing through old files containing _\n- audio\n- video",
        "answer": "audio",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "In an abandoned mansion, a forensics team is inspecting a crime scene. Next to the body is a metal box. \n    It contains cocaine, but it remains closed, and no one can see what is inside. The label on this metal box says heroin. \n    The lead detective, who's just arrived on the scene, crouches down to inspect the metal box. He cannot see what is inside the metal box, but he reads the label. He is delighted to have found this metal box.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. He specializes in cases which involve metal cans filled with drugs such as _\n- cocaine\n- heroin",
        "answer": "cocaine",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Inside the fridge of the Airbnb host's kitchen is a can labeled as \"tuna\". \n    However, the can actually contains sardines and no tuna. Jill, a guest who just arrived at the house, opens the fridge and sees the can. \n    she cannot see what is inside the can, and doesn't notice the label. She is delighted to have found this can.",
        "question": "Question: Fill in the blank with the best option. She loves eating _\n- sardines\n- tuna",
        "answer": "sardines",
        "num_states": -1,
        "num_highlights": []
    }
]